Finding aid for the Barbara Aziz broadcasts collection
Bentley Historical Library
- Radio Tahrir and related material, 1989-2014
  - August 24, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:59:33); (Ibish comments on US bombing of Sudan purported weapons factory, Sudan-Africa states relations; Karahan reports on Turkey with political, Jad Abumrad reports on January 1998 Ramadan interfaith at NY-St John Divine Cathedral and US anti-Muslim actions. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Jad Abumrad. Interviewees/Guests: political observer Hussein Ibish; Turkey observer Hurriyet Karahan; speakers from Interfaith Ramadan ifthar. Topics: Sudan, US military bombing, ramifications of earthquake in Turkey, Islam, Ramadan interfaith, Islam, civil rights.)
  - September 7, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:58:51); (Mirza describes goals and nature of magazine "Al-Talab"; Qurashi comments on media Muslim US images, and Muslim marginalization and use of theater. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: producer Jad Abumrad, Theater director Ibrahim Qurashi, UCLA magazine editor Sekina Mirza. Topics: Muslim American publishing, media bias, Muslim and Arab, political observer Hussein Ibish.)
  - September 14, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:29:32); (From 1993 archive, part 2 (instruments) of 5 part series of Arab music history. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: oud virtuoso and teacher musician Simon Shaheen. Topics: Arab music.)
  - September 28, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 1:02:13); (Abumrad's production from NY St John Divine Interfaith Ramadan, Middleton reports and voices from the NY Muslim Day Parade, Aisha Adawiya interviews sisters who assist Muslim women in need. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Jad Abumrad, Interfaith participants, Aisha Adawiya, Kairiah A. Latif, Muslim Day parade report by Nadja Middleton, Jordan Catholic relief in Iraq director, Father Mousa Adely. Topics: 1998 Ramadan, Interfaith, Muslim Day parade, Muslim Americans; Iraq refugees in Jordan, Muslim women project to assist homeless.)
  - October 5, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:59:08); (Aziz reviews Iranian film "Children of Heaven", S. Ahmed reviews conditions in Sudan criticizing media bias and interviews "Salam Sudan" peace organization Al-Tenai; Ibish report on Florida conference of American Muslim Alliance. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: NJ-activist Dr Sapphire Ahmed, Hashem Al-Tenai, political observer Hussein Ibish, producer Jad Abumrad. Topics: Iranian film, Sudan, Muslim Americans, American Muslim Alliance.)
  - October 26, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:54:45); (Zogby reviews Arab Americans in local elections, NJ candidate G. Shamy shares his ideals and aims, Dr. Sayeed on strategies for Muslim Americans in local politics, Fernandez reports on success overturning secret evidence in case of Hani Khireddin. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: NJ-candidate G. Shamy, Arab Amererican Institute director Jim Zogby (AAI), Agha Sayeed, head of Muslim American Alliance, civil rights attorney Regis Fernandez. Topics: American elections, Arab Americans, Rumi Sufi poetry, secret evidence, Muslim American civil rights.)
  - November 2, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:20); (Saad and Gage review detentions of US Muslims and fight against US government use of secret evidence, and calls from listeners; Abumrad's report from US Muslim conference Chicago. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: attorney Houeida Saad and Kit Gage of National Coalition to Protect Political Freedom (NCPPF), Jad Abumrad report. Topics: VA-based attorney Houeida Saad, civil rights, secret evidence, Muslim American rights, US Muslim conference.)
  - November 9, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:58:19); (Fr Adely appeals for relief for Iraq under sanctions and provides figures of Iraq refugees; Ben Yusuf reports on results of Arab American candidates across US; Ibish reviews Palestine-Israel negotiations Sharm El-Sheik meeting; Abumrad reports from Lebanon regarding political instability and needs. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Jad Abumrad, Asma Ben Yusuf of Arab American Institute (AAI), political observer Hussein Ibish, Catholic relief official in Jordan, Fr. Mousa Adley. Topics: Iraq, US bombing Iraq, Iraq relief, US elections, Arab American political candidates, Palestine-Israeli negotiations; Lebanon politics.)
  - November 16, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:58:18); (Bouziane reviews and interviews (French-English) Algerian Rai vocalist Cheb Mami, poet Handal speaks about her book "The Never Field," with readings. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Anissa Bouziane, Algerian vocalist Cheb Mami, NY-Based poet Nathalie Handal, political observer Hussein Ibish. Topics: Algeria, Rai music, Cheb Mami, Arab American literature, poetry, Arab women, Palestine, US policy.)
  - December 21, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:56:50); (Gonzalez's poetic music production for Ramadan, Jan Abumrad's reports on century athlete Mohammed Ali, Aziz reviews Ramadan Children's story; Nurridin leads discussion with Samad and Mohammed on diversity and Arab-centric Islam. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz, Jad Abumrad. Interviewees/Guests: Sufi musician Ibrahim Gonzalez, NJ-Seton Hall U. Prof Yusuf Nurridin, Kaseem Mohammed, Sayeed Abdul Samad. Topics: Ramadan, Islam, Mohammed Ali, Muslim Americans, African American Muslims.)
  - December 27, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:54:16); (A special Ramadan edition: Diouf, author of "Servants of Allah" on Muslim history in the Caribbean; guest children recite Qur'an, guide for fasting and observance. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: NY-based author Sylvian Diouf, Women in Islam director Aisha Adawiya, NY-area Muslim children. Topics: Islam, Caribbean-American Muslim history, Qur'an, Ramadan.)
  - December 29, 1999, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:48:44); (A special Ramadan Edition (pt2), Sudan women's Islamic recitation, children's Qur'anic reading recitation; children reading Ramadan children's story; Gonzalez sufi music production. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: NJ-Muslim rep Sapphire Ahmed, US-Sudanese children; Sufi musician Ibrahim Gonzalez. Topics: Islam, Ramadan, Sudan, Sudanese women, Muslim children; Sufi production.)
  - 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:30:24); ("Western Representations of the Muslim Woman," discussed by author Kahf. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: author, poet, and professor at University of Arkansas Mohja Kahf. Topics: Muslim women, Arab women, Oriental, media and literary images.)
  - 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:10:32); (Al-Ashkar reports on attempts to recruit him as an FBI informant. Interviewees/Guests: Al-Ashkar, visiting Palestinian student in USA. Topics: Muslim and Arab civil rights, Palestinian student, harassment by FBI, US detention.)
  - 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:33:08); (Arnove reports on bombing of Iraq and arrival of a decade of sanctions and growth of opposition to the embargo, criticism of US media and US policy; Flounders overviews global opposition to UN sanctions. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: book editor Anthony Arnove, "Iraq Under Sanctions," Sara Flounders IAC (International Action Center) director; Iraqi doctors' reports of improvements. Topics: Iraq, US bombing Iraq, anti-sanctions actions, Iraqi musician Fawzi Al-Aini.)
  - January 4, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:55:05); (1 hour discussion with musical examples with virtuoso Kayhan Kalhor. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Iran musician Kayhan Kalhor. Topics: music, Iran.)
  - January 6, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:52); (Gonzalez interviews Moore about personal, spiritual, and global issues of Ramadan. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: 3rd edition Ramadan Special --PA-based poet Abdul Hayy Moore, Sufi musician Ibrahim Gonzalez. Topics: Ramadan poetry, music, Islam, Muslim Americans.)
  - February 22, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:44); (Aziz reviews books ("War on the Top of the World", "War, Lies and Videotape"), interviews from Iraq with Iraqi doctors on health medical conditions, listener callins. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: reports by various Iraqi doctors, listener calls. Topics: Iraq, sanctions, medical reports, listeners callins.)
  - April 25, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:51:37); (Aziz comment on Palestinian music, 3 guests report and comment on this anti-Arab feature film (and other films) and planned public protests, film review, listener callins. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: 3 NY-area students, Osama Cortaz, Ramsey Kassam, and Samar Al-Balusi. Topics: US film "Rules of Engagement", anti-Arab media defamation, Iranian films by Majid Majidi.)
  - May 2, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:07); (Aziz reviews film "The Color of Paradise" by Majid Majidi, Ibish comments on US TV and film portrayal of Arabs and Muslims, listeners calls. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: political observer Hussein Ibish. Topics: Iran, Iranian films, US film on Arab themes.)
  - May 30, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:58:59); (Kit Gage updates on history of US government use of secret evidence and detentions of Arab and Muslim Americans and civil rights fight against it; comment on the liberation of South Lebanon, with listener calls. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Kit Gage Director of DC-based NCPPF. Topics: secret evidence, civil rights, Lebanon.)
  - June 3, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:58:15); (Gage updates on struggle to overturn secret evidence, listener calls, Lebanon. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Kit Gage, director of NCPPF. Topics: secret evidence, civil rights, Arab American literature, Lebanon.)
  - June 6, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:59:33); (Court update regarding secret evidence, Kiblan reviews government use of secret evidence against her client and others; Gonzalez reads his memoir, NY-based novelist Shaw Dallal interview (by Aziz), with reading by Steve Howard. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: VA-based attorney Melia Kiblan, sufi musician Ibrahim Gonzalez, Arab American author Shaw J. Dallal, writer of book "Scattered Like Seeds". Topics: Mazen Al-Najjar, Anwar Haddam, Civil rights, Muslim Americans, secret evidence, Latino Muslim, Arab American literature.)
  - June 13, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:55:02); (Samara describes economic and political coincidence of conditions in Palestine post-Oslo, and decline of agricultural sector, Ibish comments on passing of Hafiz Al-Assad and post-Al-Assad. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Palestinian editor and economist Dr Adel Samara, political observer Hussein Ibish. Topics: Palestine, Palestinian economy, Israeli occupation policy on Palestine, Syria.)
  - June 20, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:55:31); (Lecture by Nawal El-Saadawi at NY Brecht Forum, mixed with readings from "Daughter of Isis" by Nadja Middleton. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Egyptian author Nawal El-Saadawi, Nadja Middleton. Topics: Arab women, Middle East, Media.)
  - June 27, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:58:34); (Tamather Al-Akhil reads from her stories, their ancient origins, her reading style and playwriting; Aziz interviews Donni George in Baghdad speaking about status of Iraq National museum, archeology dig-sites, and antiquities under UN sanctions. Hosts/Producer: Nadja Middleton. Interviewees/Guests: Author/storyteller/actress Tamather Al-Akhil, Baghdad-based Iraq Archeologist Donni George. Topics: Arab American literature, Iraqi history, UN sanctions, archeology.)
  - July 4, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:58:24); (Brief book review of "The Road to Hell" by M. Marin; Aziz comments on US media anti-Muslim biases; Al-Taii gives overview of Iraqi history and commentary regarding Iraq-Kuwait history by Ibish, UN Iraqi ambassador comment. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: WBAI Producer Chung Yun, Book review of "The Road to Hell" by M. Marin, NC Sociology Professor Iraqi Dr. Al-Taii, political observer Hussein Ibish, Iraq UN Ambassador Nizar Hamdoon. Topics: Iraq history, Kuwait.)
  - July 18, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:56:57); (President of American Committee on Jerusalem Khalidi comments on Camp David (Clinton Administration) Israel-Palestine talks and issues; Lamis Andoni comments on Palestinian right of return and US-led Israel-Palestinian talks. Hosts/Producer: Hussein Ibish. Interviewees/Guests: Chicago University Prof. Rashid Khalidi, Boston-based journalist Lamis Andoni. Topics: Palestine-Israeli talks, Palestinian rights, Jerusalem, right of return, US policy, Israeli occupation.)
  - August 1, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:57:08); (Masri describes exploitation and corruption precipitated by sanctions policy, Flounders analyzes US economic fallout from US military policy and Iraq conditions and exploitation of Iraq under UN sanctions. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Human rights activist Rania Masri of anti-Iraq sanctions movement, Sara Flounders of International Action Center. Topics: Iraq, UN sanctions/embargo, 10-year anniversary of Iraq sanctions & Kuwait invasion, opposition to sanctions.)
  - August 8, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:52:19); (Al-Arian updates regarding imprisonment of Mazen Al-Najjar and government use of secret evidence, with commentary by Ibish, Andoni reports on Boston "Al-Awda" conference on "Right of Return". Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Boston-based journalist Lamis Andoni, US-Palestinian activist Dr. Sami Al-Arian of, political observer Hussein Ibish NCPPF. Topics: secret evidence, Muslim and Arab American civil rights, occupied Palestine, Israeli military, Palestine "'Al-Awda--Right of Return".)
  - August 29, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:42:48); (Sayeed updates role of Muslim Americans in American elections, Randa Jamal and other organizers define plans for Washington rally. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Dr Agha Sayeed, director of the American Muslim Alliance, Palestine activists Randa Jamal and Nihaya Dugan. Topics: Muslim Americans, local elections, Palestine "Right of Return" rally, Israel-Palestine, US policy.)
  - September 5, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:29:31); (Ibish analyzes recent parliamentary elections in Lebanon. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: political observer Hussein Ibish. Topics: Lebanon, elections in Lebanon, democracy, political parties.)
  - September 12, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:33:27); (Al-Najjar recounts his harassment and mistreatment by federal authorities. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Mazen (also Mazin) Al-Najjar, US-Palestinian scholar, imprisoned, deported. Topics: American Muslims, civil rights.)
  - September 16, 2000, (Special on Palestine)
    - Part 1 of 2, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 1:34:11); (Interview, reports from street rallies worldwide; Samira Smehr describes Israeli residency rules. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: 3 hr special on Palestine, political observer Hussein Ibish, Palestinian attorney (in NY) organizer Samira Smehr, Bethlehem leader, Chicago University Prof Rashid Kahlidi Mohammed Jeradad. Topics: Palestine, right of return claims, West Bank, Haifa Israel and DC Rally for Palestine.)
    - Part 2 of 2, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 1:24:22); (Interview, reports from street rallies worldwide, report from Amira Soleh. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: speakers from DC Rally: Dr. Prasad Venegopal, Amira Soleh, Seliman Fahmawi of "Committee for Defense of Uprooted in Israel", Rabiah Sahyoun in London, Dihesh camp member Ziad Abbas. Topics: Palestine, right of return claims, West Bank, Haifa, Israel; DC Rally for Palestine.)
  - September 19, 2000
    - Part 1 of 2, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 1:08:05); (Aziz reviews Muslim Americans entering public office, Saleh Shahid on his run for state senate in Rhode Island, professor of religion Ahmed discusses her Egypt memoir "A Border Passage", Gage on actions to repeal secret evidence. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Topics: Laila Ahmed, Egypt, Muslim American candidates, Arab American literature, secret evidence.)
    - Part 2 of 2, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:56:48); (Bad distortion at beginning; interview with Shaid is duplicate, interview with author Laila Ahmed is part 1. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Topics: Arab American literature, Laila Ahmed, Egypt, memoir.)
  - September 26, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:49:49); (Kit Gage update on actions to repeal secret evidence, civil rights, Muslim Americans. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Kit Gage (NCPPF), NJ political candidate H Fahmy, Aisha Adawiya (Dir. of Women in Islam), Maurii Saalakan. Topics: secret evidence, civil rights.)
  - October 3, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:59:19); (Abbas direct from Gaza regarding attacks underway in occupied territories; Maksoud comments on possible political and diplomatic UN actions at peace and criticism of US policy on Israel-Palestine. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Palestinian journalist Ziad Abbas from Bethlehem; DC-based professor at American University in DC, Dr Clovis Maksoud. Topics: Palestine uprising, Israeli occupation and military attacks on Palestinians and resistance.)
  - October 10, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:58:47); (Iraq UN ambassador Hasan reports on developments in Iraq, new flights to Iraq, erosion of sanctions, reading and interview by Kazim Ali, Atshan reports from West Bank on continued occupation and deaths. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Iraq UN Ambassador Hasan, Palestinian Ramallah-based psychologist Laila Atshan, Arab American poet Kazim Ali. Topics: Iraq, UN sanctions, Arab American literature, Kazim Ali.)
  - December 26, 2000, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 1:05:49); (Special Christmas show with various world music, commentary. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: special Christmas show. Topics: civil rights, music.)
  - 2001, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:23:56); (Director of Adameer describes conditions of prisoners and Israeli arrests. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: director of Ramallah-based prisoner organization Adameer. Topics: Palestine-Israeli, Palestine fight for rights, prisoner conditions, 2nd Intifadah.)
  - January 16, 2001, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:48:47); (Iraq: How Can I Forget?" 1995 audio documentary by BN Aziz, program marking 10 years of US assault on Iraq, Al-Bayoumi (former UN administrator in Iraq) comments on military actions on civilians and other policy. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: various Iraqi children and poets, Dr. Ashraf Al-Bayoumi (scientist). Topics: Iraq, US military policy, Middle East, anti-sanctions action, world music.)
  - January 23, 2001, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 1:00:58); (Sana Abourezk, author of "Oh Boy, I Don\'t Believe It's Soy" shares Arab recipes, Ibish assesses 8 years of Clinton administration Middle East peace efforts and examines the negotiating team and prospects for future under President Bush. Hosts/Producer: Hussein Ibish. Interviewees/Guests: US-Arab food author Sana Abourezk interviewed by Aziz, political observer Hussein Ibish. Topics: Arab food and culture, vegetarian, Middle East, US policy.)
  - January 30, 2001, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:52:42); (Bayina Sabour and Sabah discuss domestic violence and rape crisis intervention and how mosque communities can address it, F. Boyle traces US policy and sanctions towards Libya and Lockerbie case. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: NY Brooklyn Mosque leaders Sister Bayina Sabour and Brother Rabah; University of Illinois law Professor Frances Boyle. Topics: domestic violence, Muslim Americans, social services, Middle East, Libya, sanctions.)
  - February 6, 2001, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:27:40); (Aziz reviews Iranian, Egyptian and other Arab films showing at NY-NJ film festivals, with clips from reviewed films. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Aziz reviews and commentaries. Topics: film, art, Iran, Middle East, Egypt, Majid Majidi, Bahman Ghobadi.)
  - February 13, 2001, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:56:41); (Nawa reviews conditions of Afghanistan's drought, humanitarian relief and civil war, Dan Winters announces Denver conference for actions supporting Iraq. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Afghani American journalist Fariba Nawa, Colorado activist Dan Winters. Topics: Afghanistan, Iraq anti-sanctions activism.)
  - March 6, 2001, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:55:22); (Al-Mukthar (at Iraq conference in Baghdad) reviews illegality of sanctions as international terrorism, and world public reaction to embargo, reading of poems by of SV Attallah and Etel Adnan. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: London based attorney Sabah Al-Mukthar, head of Arab Lawyers Guild in UK. Topics: Iraq, UN sanctions, world music with poetry readings.)
  - March 13, 2001, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:53:50); (Nasir Zakeria and Moh Dagman interview Khalife (Arabic and English translation), about Arab music and politics and art in music and life with music clips, Laurent interviewed in Baghdad describes work with Iraq street children, Gonzalez Arab and Latino music composition and comment. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: international musician activist Marcel Khalife, Sufi musician Ibrahim Gonzalez, French volunteer Golam Laurant. Topics: world music, Arab music, Lebanon, Marcel Khalife, Sufi, Ibrahim Gonzalez, Iraq, children under UN sanctions.)
  - April 3, 2001, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:55:10); (Interviewed in Baghdad, Buthaina Nasri speaks about breaking UN sanctions on Iraq with books, Abdul Baki speaks about her latest novel "Ghost Songs" with passages read by Sybil Wong. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Cairo-based Iraq publisher and author Buthaina Nasri, US-based novelist Kathryn Abdul Baki. Topics: Iraq, women, Middle East, Arab literature, anti-intellectual sanctions, Kathryn Abdul Baki, world music.)
  - April 10, 2001, 1 digital audio files (Duration: 0:55:19); (Altoush and Kudos describe student union attempts to petition Canadian government criticizing Israeli policy, Khankan reports of attempts to include Muslim representative in Interfaith NY radio program, listener callins. Hosts/Producer: Barabara Nimri Aziz. Interviewees/Guests: Canadian Concordia University students Samer Altoush, Christina Kudos, NY-Muslim community leader Gazi Khankan. Topics: petitions in support of Palestine rights, Israel-Palestine relations, Muslim Americans.)